<resources>
    <string-array name="matches_names">
        <item>James Howlett</item>
        <item>Jean Grey</item>
        <item>Scott Summers</item>
        <item>Jubilation Lee</item>
        <item>Piotr Nikolaievitch </item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="matches_desc">
        <item>
            He\'s the best and what he does. But what he does isn\'t very nice.
        </item>
        <item>
            Jean Grey is a member of a subspecies of humans known as mutants, who are born with
            superhuman abilities. She was born with telepathic and telekinetic powers.
            Her powers first manifested when she saw her childhood friend being hit by a car.
            She is a caring, nurturing figure, but she also has to deal with being an Omega-level
            mutant and the physical manifestation of the cosmic Phoenix Force. Jean Grey experienced
            a transformation into the Phoenix in the X-Men storyline \"The Dark Phoenix Saga\". She has
            faced death numerous times in the history of the series. Her first death was under her guise
            as Marvel Girl, when she died and was \"reborn\" as Phoenix in \"The Dark Phoenix Saga\".
            This transformation led to her second death, which was suicide, though not her last.
        </item>
        <item>
            Cyclops is a member of a subspecies of humans known as mutants, who are born with
            superhuman abilities. Cyclops can emit powerful beams of energy from his eyes.
            He cannot control the beams without the aid of special eyewear which he must wear
            at all times. He is typically considered the first of the X-Men,
            a team of mutant heroes who fight for peace and equality between mutants and humans,
            and one of the team\'s primary leaders.
        </item>
        <item>
            Jubilee is a member of the human subspecies known as mutants, born with superhuman abilities.
            She can generate pyrotechnic energy blasts from her hands. Introduced as an orphaned
            \"mall rat\" from Beverly Hills, Jubilee joined the X-Men in the early 1990s,
            becoming the team\'s youngest member and often playing a sidekick role to her
            father-figure, Wolverine.
        </item>
        <item>
            A Russian mutant, he is a member of the X-Men. Colossus is able to transform
            himself into metallic form, making him the physically strongest of the team.
            Even when his powers are not engaged, he is still a physically imposing figure
            of 6 ft 7 in (200 cm). He is portrayed as quiet, honest, and virtuous.
            He has had a fairly consistent presence in X-Men-related comic books since his debut.
            A talented artist, he only reluctantly agrees to use his powers in combat,
            feeling it is his responsibility to use his abilities for the betterment
            of human and mutant-kind.
        </item>
    </string-array>
    <array name="matches_picture">
        <item>@drawable/wolverine</item>
        <item>@drawable/jeangrey</item>
        <item>@drawable/cyclops</item>
        <item>@drawable/jubilee</item>
        <item>@drawable/colossus</item>
    </array>
</resources>